quickbooksonline.com 2002-12-15

# Privacy Statement

|  **QuickBooks 2002, QuickBooks.com & QuickBooks Online Edition Privacy Statement**

[](https://www.truste.org/validate/8257) At Intuit, we dedicate ourselves to revolutionizing the way individuals manage their financial lives and small businesses manage their business. In that effort, we respect and protect the privacy of those who visit or use our Web sites. When we collect information from you, we want you to know how it is used. To demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices, we have adopted leading industry privacy guidelines. Intuit is a Premier Sponsor of TRUSTe and a member of the TRUSTe Privacy Program.

This privacy statement defines privacy aspects specific to QuickBooks, QuickBooks.com, QuickBooks Online Edition, and affiliated Intuit Web servers (together referred to as the "QuickBooks Web sites"). It serves as an adjunct to the [Intuit Online Privacy Policy](http://privacy.intuit.com/policies/), which represents our general privacy philosophy and governs all of our Web sites. The QuickBooks Web site's privacy practices are consistent and compliant with that policy.

Because of the financial nature of our business, our products & services are not designed to appeal to children under the age of 13. Therefore, we don't knowingly attempt to solicit or receive any information from children.

**Our Philosophy and Practices**  
At Intuit, we want you to feel comfortable and confident when using our product and Web site. Therefore, we would like to share with you the following principles that govern our information practices and other privacy aspects of our products and Web sites:

  * We provide you notice of our information practices.
  * We tell you how and why we use Web technologies.
  * We give you choices about how the personally identifiable information that you provide to us may be used.
  * We let you update or correct your personally identifiable information.
  * We work to protect personally identifiable information from loss, misuse and unauthorized alteration.
  * We provide various ways for you to contact us about our information practices and other aspects of privacy.

**We provide you notice of our information practices.**  
To maximize the value of our services, we may request information from you when you visit our Web sites or register our products. When we collect information from you, we'll tell you what is being collected, by whom it is being collected, to whom it may be disclosed, and how it will be used. We identify the information that is necessary to fulfill your request. Whenever we ask for additional or optional information, we identify those fields appropriately so that you know what is required to provide the requested service.

Whenever you register a product or service, we request certain personally identifiable information, including your name, address, phone number, e-mail address and company name. We do not share your contact information with outside companies for their promotional use. We may, however, use this information to notify you about upcoming product upgrades and about special offers available to registered users.

In detail, here is how and why we collect and use information from you:

  * QuickBooks 2002 Software, U.S. Version
  * Automatic QuickBooks Product Update
  * QuickBooks Online Edition
  * QuickBooks Service Center
  * QuickBooks Merchant Account Service
  * QuickBooks Online Billing
  * QuickBooks Credit Check Services
  * Technical Support, QBSN and Customer Service
  * QuickBooks Affiliate Program
  * QuickBooks Business Services Login
  * Contests and Surveys
  * Newsletters
  * Submitting Suggestions

**We tell you how and why we use Web technologies.**  
Here is how and why we use some common technologies to help manage our Web site:

  * **Cookies.** A "cookie" is a small piece of information that our Web site may provide to your browser while you are at our site. QuickBooks products & services supply your browser with cookies that contain a unique identifier used to better understand Web site usage in the aggregate so that we know what areas of our site users prefer (e.g., based on the number of visits to those areas). You may receive additional cookies when you request a service through this site.

If you simply want to browse, you do not have to accept cookies from our site. Should you decide, however, that you would like to request a service and you have modified your browser settings not to accept cookies, you will need to re-set your browser to accept the cookies that we send it. Otherwise, you may not be able to use certain areas of the Web sites. Most browsers are defaulted to accept and maintain cookies.

When you use the [QuickBooks Business Services Login](https://login.quickbooks.com/) for one of the QuickBooks services, you will receive a cookie as part of the personal identification process. This cookie will be used to confirm your identity each time you wish to access one of our services. The cookie enables you to go from screen to screen without being repeatedly asked to authenticate your identity.

Third party tracking systems in use on behalf of this Web site may assign different cookies to you. These cookies may be used to track your involvement with certain links on our site to help us better understand and improve our site. You may choose not to accept these cookies and will still have full access to site functionality. These cookies do not follow you once you leave our site, nor are they linked to personal information you provide elsewhere on our site. If you have any questions about our third party tracking system, please contact us at [http://privacy.intuit.com](http://privacy.intuit.com/).

  * **Links to the Internet.** Newer versions of QuickBooks software are "Internet enabled," allowing us to deliver products, services and information via the World Wide Web. In providing these services, your QuickBooks software will sometimes link to Web sites on the Internet after you click on a link or a message within the QuickBooks software. Links leading to the Internet are distinguished by a lightning-bolt icon. After clicking on one of those links, you will pass through an Intuit server before being "re-directed" onto the Internet. This allows QuickBooks to send you to the proper Web site even if the destination Web site has changed locations. We store which message you clicked on and its location within the software prior to linking you to the Internet. Intuit servers register the Web site you request from within the software. Intuit does not register your surfing behavior after that point.
  * **Web Site and Intuit Server Usage Data.** Our Web site — as well as servers used to support Internet enabled services from within our software product — track usage data, including, for example, your IP address, your browser type and version, which pages you view, which page, if any, linked you to our site, and which link, if any, you follow off of our site. We use this data in the aggregate to better understand Web site and product activity to improve our offerings. We may also use this data to provide you a more personalized Web site experience, assistance with technical support questions, and to send you special offers, product and service updates, or other promotional materials that are relevant and tailored to your interests. If you do not wish to receive these offers or promotions, simply indicate your contact preferences during the registration process or by visiting [https://privacy.intuit.com](https://privacy.intuit.com/). We do not share your information with outside companies for their promotional use. We do not track URLs that you type into your browser, nor do we track you across the Internet once you leave our site.

**More on our general information practices:**

  * **Mandatory and Optional Information.** We identify the information that is necessary to fulfill your request. Whenever we ask for additional or optional information, we identify those fields appropriately so that you know what is required to provide the requested service. If you choose not to provide mandatory information, we will not be able to provide you with the service you are requesting.
  * **Intuit Partners and Co-branded or Third-Party Sites.** Some of the products and services we offer are provided by Intuit's business partners. To fulfill your request for such services, we will forward your customer information to our partner, as necessary. When offering partner services on an Intuit or a co-branded site, the partner who will be receiving the information will be clearly identified. The QuickBooks products and services may provide links to third-party Web sites, such as those of our business partners and online advertisers. On these sites either Intuit and/or its partners may collect information about you. Intuit is not responsible for the actions of these third parties. We encourage you to review their privacy policies to learn more about what, why and how they collect and use personally identifiable information.

  * **E-Mail Messaging.** When sending you e-mail we may use an image called a single pixel GIF, that allows us to format messages tailored to your computer's capabilities. We also use this technology to determine, in the aggregate, the number of people who open our e-mails. When you initiate a response by clicking on a link within an e-mail message, you are re-directed onto the internet. We then record your individual response to help us deliver information that is more relevant to your interests.
  * **Intuit and its Subsidiaries** Intuit and its subsidiaries may exchange customer data with each other to fulfill your request or to provide you with information about other products and services.
  * **Service Providers.** In some cases, we will employ or work with service providers such as consultants, temporary workers, third party software developers, or outsourcers to complete a business process or provide a service on our behalf. For example, we may use service providers to deliver products, offer online software applications, or send e-mails. When we employ service providers, we may need to share your personally identifiable information. Service providers are strictly prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for purposes other than to act on our behalf.
  * **Service Alerts and Critical Notices.** Although we respect and honor the privacy preferences you have expressed, we may nevertheless contact you to inform you of specific changes that may impact your ability to use this service or for other critical non-marketing purposes, such as bug alerts. We may also contact you to respond to your specific requests or to clarify the order information you provided to us.
  * **Change of Control.** Your personally identifiable information may be transferred in connection with a sale, merger, transfer, exchange or other disposition (whether of assets, stock or otherwise) of all or a portion of a business of Intuit and/or its subsidiaries. You will have the opportunity to opt out of further secondary use of your information following any change of control.
  * **Changes to Our Privacy Policy.** If we plan to make significant changes to any of our privacy policies or practices with respect to how we use personally identifiable information, we'll post those changes to the QuickBooks.com Web site 30 days before they take effect.
  * **Legal Disclosures.** In some cases we may be required to disclose certain information to comply with a legal process, such as a court order, subpoena, search warrant, or law enforcement request.

**We give you choices about how the personally identifiable information that you provide to us may be used.**  
We give you the opportunity to control the use of your personal information for purposes other than to fulfill your request. We will provide you the opportunity to opt-out of secondary uses of personally identifiable information you provide us, whenever we gather it. Simply notify us during the information collection process or go to [http://privacy.intuit.com](http://privacy.intuit.com/).

**We let you update or correct your personally identifiable information.**  
We provide you the opportunity to update or correct your personally identifiable information online using the QuickBooks Business Console, by calling (800) 335-4651.

**We work to protect personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration.**  
We employ industry recognized security safeguards to help protect the personally identifiable information that you have provided to us from loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration. Whenever we prompt you to transmit sensitive information, such as a credit card number, to us through our products or services, we support encryption of your data as it is transmitted to us.

We work to protect personally identifiable information stored on the site's servers from unauthorized access using industry standard computer security products, such as firewalls, as well as carefully developed security procedures and practices. All employees must review and sign a written statement of these practices, which include limiting access to sensitive information to only those employees who require such information and enforcing strict password protocols for all employees. We use both internal and external resources to review the adequacy of our security measures on a regular basis.

**We provide various ways to contact us about our information practices and other aspects of privacy.**  
Questions regarding the QuickBooks product & service privacy statement, our online privacy policy, our information practices or other aspects of privacy on our Web site should be directed to us at [http://privacy.intuit.com](http://privacy.intuit.com/) or by writing to us at Intuit Inc., Customer Communication, 2800 East Commerce Center Place, Tucson, AZ, 85706.

If we have not responded to your inquiry, or if your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, please contact [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/). Please note that TRUSTe only handles inquiries pertaining to our online practices.

**QuickBooks 2002 Software, U.S. Version**  
When you purchase QuickBooks 2002 we require you to register your purchase. During the registration process we require your name, address, phone number, e-mail address and company name. We do not share your contact information with outside companies for their promotional use. We may, however, use this information to notify you about upcoming product upgrades and about special offers available to registered QuickBooks users about this or other Intuit products and services, or those of our partners. If you do not wish to receive notification of future product upgrades and be eligible for special offers, you may opt out of contact at the time of registration. After registration, you may contact us regarding your privacy preferences at [http://privacy.intuit.com](http://privacy.intuit.com/) or write to us at:

> Intuit Inc.  
>  Customer Communication  
>  2800 East Commerce Center Place  
>  Tucson, AZ 85706

After completing the product registration process, we provide you the opportunity to create a [QuickBooks Business Services Login](https://login.quickbooks.com/). The QuickBooks Business Services Login verifies your identity and will allow you to enjoy faster access to QuickBooks branded product and services.

Finally, we request that you answer some general questions about yourself and your business and how you use the QuickBooks product. This information will help us continue to improve our products and services to better meet your needs. Answering these questions is optional, and you will be able to register your product without completing these sections. If you choose to provide Intuit this information, we may use it to contact you about special offers that may be of interest to you. This information may also be used in aggregate form to help us evaluate our products and services.

**Automatic QuickBooks Product Update**  
Intuit works year-round to make QuickBooks better. From time to time, we place updates on our Web site for customers to download. An update might include a timesaving new feature, minor repairs to keep software running smoothly, or timely information relevant to customers' businesses.

You can obtain these downloads in several different ways. The easiest is by using QuickBooks' Automatic Update feature. When an important update is available, QuickBooks uses the current Internet connection to download and install the update. Everything happens in the background, without disturbing current tasks or slowing down the computer. The software is updated while you work.

With the Automatic Update feature, QuickBooks only connects to Intuit servers when you are already connected to the Internet. You always have the option of turning off this feature. To do this, go to the "File" menu within QuickBooks, select "Update QuickBooks" then click the "Update Options" link and follow the instructions.

You may obtain the same updates by going to "Update QuickBooks" screen and clicking on "Update". You may also manually download program updates by visiting http://www.quickbooks.com/support/updates.html.

The update feature transmits technical information to Intuit about the computer's connection and the QuickBooks software being updated. A secure connection protects customer-sensitive information during an update. Under no circumstances do Intuit servers access or read any other information on your computer. During an update, QuickBooks downloads only the necessary files to your PC.

**QuickBooks Online Edition**  
We gather information from you at various times during your usage of the product. Below we detail the point at which we take the information, what information we gather and how we use the information.

> **Startup Interview/Registration:** We collect your company contact information, which we use to contact you regarding the service. We may use your contact information to alert you regarding product changes, upgrades, and other special Intuit offers. To opt out simply indicate your preference at the time of registration, or contact us at [http://privacy.intuit.com](http://privacy.intuit.com/). We also collect information about your business, such as your industry, the number of employees you have, the type of ownership structure of your business, and outstanding loans your business may have. We use this information to customize the Chart of Accounts so that it accurately tracks the kind of activity your business will have, such as loan payments or tax filings. Lastly, we ask you to setup a Login Name, Password and Challenge Questions for use in logging in to QuickBooks Online Edition. Your password is encrypted on our servers, and no Intuit employee has access to it. QuickBooks Online Edition uses the [QuickBooks Business Services Login](https://login.quickbooks.com/) process to simplify your access to this and our other services.
> 
> **General Product Use:** No financial information you enter when using QuickBooks Online Edition will be used or shared except as required to fulfill a service you request.
> 
> **Preferences:** In this section of the product your company name and contact information are stored and modifiable. This information is used in the communications and forms you generate in QuickBooks Online Edition, for example the statements and e-mails that you send to your customers.
> 
> **Billing/Subscription:** We collect your credit card information, solely for the use of billing you for QuickBooks Online Edition.

Additionally, QuickBooks Online Edition uses its server logs to gather usage information. This allows us to better understand product performance, activity, and utilization. The information is used in the aggregate to improve the product.

QuickBooks Online Edition takes many precautions to safeguard your company information. You must access our product through a secure connection, protecting your information as it travels over the Internet. Also, our servers are backed up nightly, and those backups are stored remotely so that your information is safer in the event of a natural disaster.

**QuickBooks Service Center**  
The QuickBooks Service Center provides one location where you can log in for services, navigate to other services, maintain access and account information, set up subscriptions and payment methods, and receive notices and alerts for services you have subscribed to. If you wish to access the QuickBooks Service Center we ask you to use the [QuickBooks Business Services Login](https://login.quickbooks.com/) process. A company and user account will be created with your company name, user name, e-mail, address, phone and fax numbers. In addition to establishing your Service Center account, we may use this information to notify you about upcoming product upgrades and about special offers we make available to QuickBooks Service Center users about this or other Products or services or those of our partners. If you do not wish to receive notification of future product upgrades and be eligible for special offers, you may opt out during the information collection process or by contacting us at [http://privacy.intuit.com](http://privacy.intuit.com/).

We gather information from you at various times during your use of the QuickBooks Service Center. No financial information you enter when using QuickBooks Service Center will be shared except as required to fulfill a service you request. Below we detail the point at which we take the information, what information we gather and how we use the information:

> **Managing the Company:** This feature allows company administrators to update company and user information such as company name, login name, address, phone number, e-mail, as well as add or delete users and specify user rights. User login name and e-mail address are used to notify the user of changes in access or use rights. For example, when requesting access for a new user, you will be asked to provide the e-mail address of the new user. The e-mail address will be used to send an e-mail invitation to the new user with instructions on how to access the QuickBooks Service Center.
> 
> **Subscription and Payment Information:** This feature allows you to view and update services that you currently subscribe to. It also allows you to set up payment methods for these services or services you may be interested in subscribing to. When you subscribe to a new service, your company name and e-mail address may be provided to the service you're requesting. Credit card information is used only to provide payment to the services you have subscribed to. We do not share your credit card information with third parties except as required to provide payment for the services you have subscribed to.

**QuickBooks Merchant Account Service**  
The QuickBooks Merchant Account Service allows you to accept payment by credit card from your customers by phone, mail, in-person, or online when used with QuickBooks Online Billing. To use this service your company must apply for a merchant account with one of our merchant bank partners. To apply for the Merchant Account Service, you will be required to supply the bank your company name, address, phone number, e-mail address, description of your products and/or services and detailed financial and operational information on your company. This information is used by the merchant bank for making a credit decision on your application. If they extend you credit, you become their customer and become subject to their privacy practices. Please see their privacy statements for further details on their practices.

If your application for an account is approved, information sufficient to uniquely identify your account is shared by our merchant bank partner with our Internet transaction processor partner, and then forwarded to Intuit. This information includes company name, address, phone and e-mail address. This information is used by the Internet transaction processor partner only for the purpose of fulfilling the transaction. On occasion, we may also use your contact information to send you special offers on Intuit products or services or those of our partners, which may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive such communications, simply indicate your contact preferences during the registration process or by contacting us at [http://privacy.intuit.com](http://privacy.intuit.com/).

QuickBooks Merchant Account Service allows you to process your customer payments directly from QuickBooks, so you do not have to re-enter transaction information. To enable this service, the transaction information you enter into the software is sent to an Intuit server and to the Internet transaction processor. Once confirmed, the transaction is updated in QuickBooks and your transaction information is sent to the merchant bank partner for settlement. For the security of your transactions and your convenience, the Internet transaction processor also keeps a record of the status of the transactions you've processed, so you can see reports of this information at any time through a Web browser. QuickBooks may use this information to track our partner's performance and to improve the design and functionality of this service.

**QuickBooks Online Billing**  
The QuickBooks Online Billing service allows you to e-mail invoices, statements, and estimates from QuickBooks software and receive payment online from your customers. To use this service, we ask that you first sign in with QuickBooks Business Services. Currently, there are two methods of receiving payment that you can use with Online Billing: PayPal and QuickBooks Merchant Account Service (MAS). Please see the QuickBooks Merchant Account section of this statement for more details. For PayPal, both you and your customers must apply for an account with PayPal. The information collected during the PayPal registration process is governed by the [PayPal privacy policy](http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/privacy-outside) and will be used to facilitate online payments. This information may also be used in the aggregate to help us evaluate our products and services.

> When you e-mail an invoice, statement, or estimate using either the basic or Deluxe Online Billing services, your e-mail is transmitted via a secure connection to Intuit for formatting prior to delivery to your customer. Form data (including items, quantities, terms, customer information, amounts, and the "from", "to", and "cc", and subject lines of the e-mail) may also be stored on Intuit's servers. In the case of forms enabled for online payment, storing this information allows us to create the Web site your customers will access to pay your invoices. In the case of forms not enabled for online payment, this information may be used for support purposes, such as confirming that an invoice has been sent. In addition, the invoice form may display a URL link designed to promote usage of Online Billing or other services supported by Intuit. We monitor your customers' interactions with these links, as well as with the Online Billing Web sites, to evaluate and improve our service. The information we collect about you or your customers' usage of the Online Billing service is used to help us evaluate and improve the Online Billing service for you and your customers.
> 
> Intuit also shares invoice and/or statement data with PayPal and/or QuickBooks MAS partners, as necessary to fulfill the service, for those customers who have elected to enable payment options. If you choose not to store information on Intuit servers (or if you do not wish to allow limited access of the invoice data to our payment partners as applicable), you will not be able to use the Online Billing service.
> 
> The Deluxe version of the Online Billing Service includes an E-mailed Forms Delivery Tracking feature that enables the invoice sender to determine if the recipient has viewed the e-mail invoice. Viewing is tracked through the use of either a single pixel gif included in the e-mail or when a recipient clicks on a link to an online copy of the invoice. Tracking information is only for use by the invoice sender. Invoice recipients are notified of this feature through a separate e-mail message sent prior to the first use of this technology. This information may also be used in the aggregate to help us evaluate this service.

**QuickBooks Credit Check Services**  
The QuickBooks Credit Check Services allow you to get credit reports on your business customers right from QuickBooks. To use this service we ask that you first use the QuickBooks Business Services Login process to simplify your access to this and other services; then sign up for an account with Dun & Bradstreet (D&B). To sign up for an account, you must supply your name, e-mail address, company name and address, billing address, phone number, and credit card information. This information is required to register your company to use the services. On occasion, we may contact you with special offers on products and services of Intuit or one of our partners, which we think may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive such communications, simply indicate your contact preferences during the registration process or by contacting us at [http://privacy.intuit.com](http://privacy.intuit.com/).

> **Acquiring Credit Reports.** In order to get a credit report on a company you are researching, you must provide the name and state of that company. You may choose to supply additional information (such as address, phone number, and DUNS #) in order to increase the confidence level of the match. This information will be used for the sole purpose of locating the company in the D&B database, so you can then receive a company credit report, ongoing updated credit rating meters, and ongoing credit alerts (when there is business or financial news which might affect the credit rating of that company).
> 
> **Receiving Credit Alerts.** You may choose to provide a list of businesses to D&B in order to receive ongoing credit alerts. When you add a company to your Credit Alerts List, that company's name, address and phone number will be sent to D&B for the sole purpose of locating that company in the D&B database, so that D&B can send you alerts when there is business or financial news which might affect the credit rating of that company.
> 
> **Report A/R Aging Information to D &B.** You may choose to report A/R Aging Data to D&B on your selected commercial customers. When you report information, you submit the names, addresses, and payment information (displayed on your screen for review prior to submission) to D&B for the purpose of contributing to D&B's picture of your customers' payment habits. The payment information you submit will be aggregated with payment information from other sources and used as an input to D&B's credit/payment score calculations. D&B will not disclose the source of payment information on a particular company (except when requested by that company's owner, and only when five or more vendors have submitted data, in which case the sources are identified alphabetically, preventing any match-up to the specific payment experiences). D&B will not send marketing or other communications to your customers. When you submit your information to D&B, the customer name, address and payment information is sent from your computer directly to D&B.

**Technical Support, QBSN, and Customer Service**

**Technical Service Plan Enrollment.** Premier Service Plans may be purchased directly from our Web site. We collect your name, address, e-mail, telephone number, QuickBooks software registration number, and payment information. We use this information to register you with the service plan that you have selected. We may use this information to contact you for renewals of service, newsletters or other marketing purposes.

**QuickBooks Support Network (QBSN) Members Only Area.** If you are a registered member of this network, we ask you to log in using your [QuickBooks Business Services Login](https://login.quickbooks.com/). Within this area, you may submit electronic incidents, chat online with a support engineer, review your case history, update your name, business name, address, phone number, e-mail address, fax number, subscribe/unsubscribe to the QBSN e-mail bulletin, submit feedback, and review online newsletters and other tips.

To submit a question, we will require you to provide certain information about your QuickBooks product, such as version or platform. We will use this information to research and respond to your issue.

**Customer Service Online Chat.** We offer you the opportunity to chat online with our sales and service advisors. When ordering or registering products through our online chat service, we ask for your name, address, phone number, and e-mail address to process your order. On occasion, we may contact you with special offers that may interest you. We may share your name and address with selected financial institutions that offer products that may interest you. If you do not wish to receive such communications, simply indicate your contact preferences at the time you place the order or contact us at [http://privacy.intuit.com](http://privacy.intuit.com/). Credit card information is used only to provide payment for the products you have ordered. We do not share credit card information with third parties except as required to process your payment.

**QuickBooks Affiliate Program**  
Through the QuickBooks Affiliate Program, you can place a QuickBooks logo on your Web site and earn commissions by selling QuickBooks products. If you are interested in becoming a QuickBooks Affiliate, we ask you to provide your name, address, phone number, e-mail and other information about your Web site. We use the information from your application to determine your suitability for this program. If you become a QuickBooks Affiliate, Intuit or our agents use the information to contact you about updates to the product and program and to provide you with newsletters and other information to help you become more successful in the Affiliate Program. We also encourage you to read the QuickBooks Affiliate Agreement located at the Affiliate Program Web pages.

**QuickBooks Business Services Login**  
Many of our products and services use the QuickBooks Business Services Login process. During the sign-up process, we request a username, password, e-mail address, and a challenge question and answer. The information you give us is used to provide you a single login that can be used to verify your identity and grant you access to QuickBooks branded products and services. If you do not want to create a QuickBooks Business Services Login, you may opt out during the registration process, and you will have the opportunity to create the login again when you register for additional services. The login process has been created to make regular use of our services easier for you. The QuickBooks Business Services Login, however, does not replace registration for our products and services. We may also use the information you provide to notify you about upcoming product upgrades and about special offers we make available to QuickBooks users. If you do not wish to receive notification of future product upgrades or be eligible for special offers, you may opt out during the registration or by contacting us at [http://privacy.intuit.com](http://privacy.intuit.com/).

**Contests and Surveys**  
From time to time, we may offer you the option to participate in contests or surveys. If you would like to participate, we may ask you for contact information, preferences, or other information. This information may be used to conduct research, improve our offerings, or award prizes. We may also ask for more specific demographic information such as age or gender to better understand who uses our site and to make the site more useful for you. Our contests may have separate rules and we will identify how the information that you supply will be used in each case.

**Newsletters**  
We provide you the opportunity to subscribe to e-mail newsletters and other e-mail communications. You may unsubscribe by following the instructions provided in each e-mail newsletter.

**Submitting Suggestions**  
Using our Web site, you can ask us questions and share comments with us. Through our submission request form, we provide you a chance to send specific questions or comments and we request, at your option, a name and e-mail address, so that we may respond to your inquiry. All submissions through this form are treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary, and may be published or used by Intuit without your personal information, for other purposes.

_Last updated 11/04/02_

|
